for their own you
to the extent that no money is left for
this all times when they go out that
they do not even have inheritance
look at the next verse is very important
but we're gonna close after we release
this verse and they'll have to make a
correction
foreign
[Music]
unless they believe
a believing woman is better than the
figure even if you like her
nor shall you permit your women to know
his pagans unless they believe I believe
in man is better than the vegan even if
you like him
they invite you help while God invites
to heaven and forgiveness in accordance
with his way he clarify his Revelations
for those who tested
so uh
let's put a party we are permitted to
very good and Christians
but you cannot marry a Muslim who does
not believe God in standing in the Quran
because
when we receive the Quran where every
page says do not worship either
and
the Quran is complete and perfect Etc et
cetera because our responsibility is
multiplied
I I mentioned before the example of
God's chosen people
and how they have been suffering and
Hitler is still six million
it's because the responsibility is
doubled from God chooses you and gives
you his message your responsibility is
problem
so when God gives you a message that
says this message is complete and
perfect and you say no it is not
complete
then you have deserved
the punishments many fold
and this is why
we are allowed to manifestions of Jews
but not a Muslim who does not believe in
Quran is
completely
and
you have to believe
that when you break this law and
yourself for a while
when you break this law and marry
an article
will suffer a lot of pain it's not worth
it you follow this law
you marry a believer
even if
you don't like him or her you
so if you're about to get married then
you ask your fiance or
to believe
and this would serve two purposes
parents
it can be approved for genuine love
he or she changes for you
second is
so you make it a condition before
marriage
and if the candidate is a Muslim who
does not believe that the Quran is
located
and you'll be far better off and you say
no I'm not going to marry you know and
continue to believe that Quran is not
complete
now if you are relaxed in this
commandment you will suffer another
thing
and the Pharisees might devotion for
carry on to the consumers
right right okay
but you're saying the Muslim can't say
is Christian or Jews
of those Christians I cannot be idle
worshipers right like a Christian that
Christian should not be Jesus worshiper
they don't look at it
and there's a
possibility that they they will become
believer
but the Muslim already looked at the
Quran and saw with his or her own eyes
that the Quran says this book is
complete and fully detailed and they
made the decision to reject that and not
to believe God that person already made
a stand and God made a stand against
that person that used to not marry him
or her
with a Christian the Christian didn't go
through that test
the person who will believe Jesus and
God the son of God
may eventually it would be easier for
that person to come to the Quran alone
then it is for a person who already
adopted the Quran and decided let us not
complete but decided not to believe
it's very difficult to change yeah
but enough for life
I'm sure there are hundreds of thousands
of pretty Egyptian girls
who don't even know honey or the others
yeah right so they're available don't
worry
okay
if you don't imagine that all of the
Muslim women already are worshipers of
Hadith some of them don't even know the
Quran nor the hadees right
yeah yeah the right one for you again
Turkish women
we're gonna have the presidential Allah
foreign
[Music]
sexual activities
to say
so there is an exception even the
Christians maybe an argument
you can see the difficulty that's
definitely been uh well 17 also the next
stage the definition of pagans are those
who say that Christ the son of Mary with
God
now
I would imagine that the majority of
Christians
[Music]
in Italian
who can say that Christ is only
there however other Christians don't
want them to be called Christians and
then that is intramural problems within
them
six o'clock in the morning
foreign
[Music]
go home instead
cartoon
in the name of that this is the merciful
subtitude is my situation they ask you
about investigation
let's say it is harmful
it's going to avoid it of course with
the women during menstruation
once they're clean you may have
intercourse with them and the manner
designated by God
loves the encounters and he loves those
who love him
so the only verse
it is a step forward
foreign
there are two words
in Arabic but designate those who you
can
and also continuously ahead and the word
used here is
the one that means continuously repent
God loves those who continuously care
those who are the pets are called
fatigue
but the Lord used here was telling me
which means they always return
and as we
've been learning the last few footballs
is that you cannot go to heaven with one
sin
you have to be sinless
to qualify because Adam and Eve
committed oneself until
and one way of erasing sin is repentance
enough to repent continuously
implemented The Habit to the extent that
when you toss around in your bed
half asleep you must
train yourself to repent
or your health conscious
just as you repentance your turn in your
bed it is
don't read it
foreign
ers
I can't think of any English word I just
we can use a multiple world and say a
couple of stores who continuously repair
one of the professions in the urban
language is
thank you
so it's uh no it's a different slight
price work for that I would
I would meet you at the airport
for the past three days
but when you bet not to break up more
ideas
there's nobody else involved except you
when I meet somebody at the airport
and then somebody depending on you
involve somebody else
that guy
the guy pledged to donate
a hundred dollars to the poor
if I press this test
now the the board even though they are
unknown is still involved in it so we
can't break them
but that's not to sin is something you
only use above it
but unless you make it at all but
it was a swearing I swear by God
there are two two kinds of expedition
because the promise the broken promise
for somebody else is involved to visit
us
at all
they're both swearing
yeah
[Music]
I was thinking that it was more like the
intentions behind me all right yeah you
know like when you say that I um you
know
I promise never to uh
stand upon the transmission or whatever
again you know extensions
and so can you see that the extensions
behind the Microsoft
yeah that's what I'm saying it does not
uh it's not the type of officers
foreign
record oh
yeah the whole thing just probably says
yeah
when you've left you will not sin again
you're supposed to be reminding yourself
on the top
never again God will extend the dentist
you have a certain weakness if you have
a habit of gossiping against other
people
I'm sorry that I will never gossip again
so I keep saying this until you read it
to come to that profession
Al
to have a bad habit of life you said
never never appear in my life
again
this is
nine percent so and you keep reminding
yourself
because you'll get rid of a bad habits
and you're getting to another bad habit
and so forth
and you're cleansing yourself one by one
so this world is very important in this
verse that God loves to continue
that the person from the verses I
describe it in that the way that to the
extent that
when you are half conscious person in
that that's good
as soon as you have questions
forgive me back to myself
because if the apply is also a
recognition of God
perfect
remember this
you can find but excuse the rest of God
that every chance we get
to us
but if you think to yourself don't never
do it again
foreign
you don't have to be a sinner
must be ready if you die now when you go
to heaven
so you have to think about this
we have to search for it
we all drive we can go drive
it must be ready
you have to be ready all the time and if
you're very mindfulness goes to heaven
is one percent not the same consent
yeah actually as a believer in God alone
you have to be determined not to have
anything in your life none
and the way to arrest him is repentance
in the sense that you cannot return are
the ones that you know or something is
wrong when you do it no one is wrong
you can't repent from that you have to
pay for it
you have to pay for your beard
that's the only alternative actually
because Point paying for it over there
means Etc
there's no such thing as pain over there
you have to pay for it here
so it could be even Steven I suppose
the rest
now this is this is where the uh
positive actions come in the face of the
five prayers today
Ramadan this is a positive thing that
erase the negatives okay
the residents because they are
almost certainly since that we're not
aware of
we passed by your brother or sister and
you didn't believe him or her
properly
but there was something on your mind
your brother sister told you you made a
face
yeah
I read somewhere that is the greatest
thing he committed before in the
seriously became a believer in one God
that these are really aware that it was
so bad when you did it red red decor and
even if you're ready maybe you had
missed that particular verse that these
are forgiven more
more easy not only forgiven they are
converted
Iran teaches that when you come for God
you know you'll come to that to address
your pensions
they'll put those High School the past
sins and uh sodium Mars
and determinism never to do it again you
actually become
credits
I remember one time I was flying
to Egypt and
there was a gentleman next to me
it was a measure of the army or
something and the different Army when he
was collecting all the bottles with
liquor from the people around him and
drinking them out
so I couldn't help tell him why you know
accumulating
a good number of sins this way
and he said are you familiar with the
Russian one that says when you
repentance to credit this idea I said
well I'm trying to estimate as many sins
as possible so I can convert them to
prayer
that was the best excuse I've ever heard
yeah
I think that was the only person ever
remember
but that's true
it's not the life of idol worship and
sin and so forth and then you declare a
great repentance
to come to God then
oil filter converted into credits
I have a feeling that this conversion to
credits a company for a polishing
process that is quite severe
but when you look when you look at what
it is doing
the judge the cleansing process and
the full version of sin for privacy this
is actually the
blessing a great blessing
the blessing interested in this guy
because everything passes all hardships
right
but the sin is in your record
on the day of judgment means
just
Quran says those who buried him as hell
commands of heaven and Triumph blessed
and contain the great fire
so it must be among the repentance those
two continuously repent
good 23.
the women are assets for you and you may
enjoy your assets however your life so
long as you maintain righteousness
you shall observe God and know that you
would ultimately meet you your good news
this is the first x-rated person that
will come across is
the Quran but the key sentences here are
investor 22 and the man is designated by
God
the key expression
and in 223 so long as you maintained
righteousness
so there are limits beyond the words
that will be abuse or misuse
next subtitle
absolute life
now how does that relate you know in
Wisconsin like this feels it seems like
this is
Within
you know that you are the confidence
that they are your confidence
what was that first that's 223
so there was the first mentioned
confidence
so it's a it's a two-way it's a two-way
street
took a long way
it takes effective lies that the men are
the ones who are usually recommended
my goodness he was so quiet this
afternoon
okay
the forgiver
equivalent
if he wasn't here then he wouldn't know
what you what your pledges were in the
first place
and if he wasn't on Mission he wouldn't
have the power to forgive them
and alhamdulillah he is forgiving and
Clement being that a governor gives
Clements
means he gives apart
man is in death we're all ready to die
for his mortal sins and he's
Governor calls a plea of Clements
Maine and the governor or something that
he has he receives Clement under his
party so God is the ultimate one
let's work the electric chair required
so it's um
people talk a lot in the you know hear
people swear a lot for us that's just
not a good practice to say God this I've
got that God damn this
is
or to use the word of the word the
powerful words of of scripture and of
God as a
part of idle conversations that worked
by the joke
I just wanted a better way of seeing
a lot of people they talk about God and
they appear to be righteous
in their speech
but really it's not what you say that's
important
you're held responsible for what you
intend to do
and what your motivation is
here we have in the Corey and what we
know from psychology the underlying
structure of human behavior is
motivation
is what you intend to do or what you're
motivated to do that makes a difference
so this is something you can read in
modern psychology which is right here in
the corner but your personal motives are
their intentions is a true way of
deciding
what they're all about not just what
they think
and sometimes the emotions are very deep
life
the motivation is the key to
understanding Human Nature of the human
mind
people can draw a line between this and
that to say something is is is one thing
and another first of all they must have
immortal
there's a very famous book on
mathematics probably laws of form which
almost unfortunately mythical in its
concession of the world the first
sentence
he demoted it prior to distinction
before we draw a boundary between A and
B we have to have a moment
foreign
he said
I said you have to pass three days or
feed 10 poor people so can I smoke now
in other words he decided to be the
first few days
but in the case of saying
I would never sin again
then the person cannot say Okay I want
to commit adoption
and you can see the
nonsense
doesn't make sense
he uh
he decided to hit some poor people and
he went on smoke
but that's not the same
the sympathy experience
foreign
that's the question
the benefits
between the forgivability and repentance
and and repentance
forgiveness if anything is forgivable
that's so far
is that
some people don't understand
the other church is either works the
extensive most choices
gave you them anything everything
so you want to choose something to
forgiven
these are the only choices
uh
we respect upon God chose him to happen
after the last scripture out of his
mouth
and the people who really love Jesus are
the ones who know him as he really is
the people who love Muhammad
a couple of practice
everything is forgivable
now we can talk about a person who
advisors
at one time they were Believers in them
Allah
you can become police
a person can be a hard divorce attorney
regardless
um
first of all the hypocrite under this
Believers give up the right to be
forgiven anyway
recognize God
foreign
so first I just believe us
and the Hypocrites are actually just
been here from the tip that works
because uh
yeah
you don't believe that this is complete
foreign
because of that no the professor said
I'm a disbeliever
you would you listen to him or her
knowing that
the person who comes to as a great
delivery
and then takes you away from the past
the last words
but aren't they weren't they at one time
I mean Hypocrites are people who
believed at one time
but many of them became believers
therefore
they put the you know
foreign
you know
I had something about Muhammad
for example
this is because we have had two people
here from Seattle who are going to go
back and hear this I just heard this
recently about
Muhammad we should it's a justification
for suiting anonymity okay and I've
heard you explain it before but they're
going to have the same thing thrown at
them okay so it's the idea that what
happened was a good model okay it's like
he he got the core in and you know he
follows it
and let's look at his life and let's
let's model our life after his life this
is justification okay and the things
that he did okay because he's the
prophet so he's a good model so let's
follow the model you know that's that's
what they're saying so that's the Quran
says
you give attention to the rich man and
they elected the poor man
and give his attention to the rich man
because he did
the God says don't do that
Quran says the prophet feared to people
instead of fearing God and because
therefore this plan is unfairish
internally before I boys have a lot of
the glasses do not follow the examples
but avoiding with one of the most common
things
listening
I want to ask you
again
foreign
yeah
no Believers Prince another Believers
except by mistakes
whatever kids are believersed by
mistakes are expired by three
okay he is not 93. but he says ask for
the one who gives a believer's delivery
investigation of his help accordingly
about it forever and God has argue with
him trust is him and that's the good for
him
because
you could not be a believer
Sy
you know
what is the magnitude says no belief or
skills except your mistake
but tonight
I said as for the one who killed the
believer
it was best executed
curses him
is even worse and has to return to him a
terrible decisions
and then whip your hundred lessons
all right
says
two beautiful reasons I realizes
the Holy Spirit
but as part of the person who has been
friends of the Lord
as far as belief is concerned we lost
utilities
and a lot of us may perceive ourselves
but when this decision the situation of
a test arises
oh
we might turn back you know and in that
case
it was the only way that we could really
know our faces to attempt
and uh
like you know again
it says um
foreign
disability
it's the time of death